UNESCO Second Canadian Archaeological Expedition to Carthage Records MS210
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Excavation site images, 1905 -- 2002; MS210.004; 7.45 Linear Feet; 1424 Digital Object(s)
  - 2CC78, 1978 -- 1979; MS210.004.004
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035 (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001 (Box 3)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00001.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002 (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00002.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003 (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00003.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004 (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00004.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005 (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - April 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00005.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - EMW 1978, MS210.004.003.00005.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - EMW 1978, MS210.004.003.00005.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - EMW 1978, MS210.004.003.00005.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - EMW 1978, MS210.004.003.00005.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006 (Box 3)
      - EMW 1978, MS210.004.003.00006.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - EMW 1978, MS210.004.003.00006.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 34, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 35, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 36, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 17, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 21, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 24, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 43, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 13, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 2, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 44, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 12, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 40, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 18, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 46, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 38, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 35, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 37, 1978; MS210.004.003.00006.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007 (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 7, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 6, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 5, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 4, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 3, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 1, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 14, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 45, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 15, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 16, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 19, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 20, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 22, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 23, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 25, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 26, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 27, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 28, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 29, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 30, 1978; MS210.004.003.00007.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008 (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 47, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 42, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 9, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 8, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 10, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 11, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 33, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 32, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CCI 31, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 7, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 5, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 40, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 3, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 2, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 1, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 15, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 10, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 11, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 9, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 12, 1978; MS210.004.003.00008.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009 (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 6, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 8, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 4, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - OH 2CC2 13, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.003.00009.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
  - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.005
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010 (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 4KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00010.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011 (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00011.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012 (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 5KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00012.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013 (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 9KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00013.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014 (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00014.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015 (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 13KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00015.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016 (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)